

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

# **Summary**

Building software for the web — experienced in the Javascript and Python ecosystem.

# Skills\_

**Languages** Javascript, Python, Perl5, C++

**Tooling** Git, Bash, Linux, Mobx, Lerna, grunt/gulp, npm/yarn

Frameworks React, Hapi, Django, Django Rest Framework, Flask, Scrapy, Microsoft SQL Server, PostgreSQL

**Industry Knowledge** CI/CD, Agile Software Development, Data Structures and Algorithms

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

Vox Sea Sdn. Bhd. Remote

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT CONSULTANT

May. 2022 - Present

· Created a Python utility library for formatting markdown text to its equivalent on several social media channels.

#### Vox Sea Sdn. Bhd.

Kuala Lumpur, Federal Territory of Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Feb. 2021 - March. 2021

- Use Django, Kubernetes, Docker, and PostgreSQL to build and deploy web applications.
- Guided junior developers through technical problems.
- Responsible for development of parts of a REST API that interacts with an AI back-end.
- Responsible for deployment of the back-end REST API using Kubernetes and Docker.
- Participated in daily scrum/agile meetings (technical) and weekly company meetings.
- Collaborated with other developers in building, and maintaining web applications.

## Binary Group Services Sdn. Bhd.

Cyberjaya, Selangor, Malaysia

Dec. 2018 - Dec. 2020

Learned and adopted new technology quickly (Javascript/Perl5).

- Use React, Grunt, Mobx, Webpack and SASS to build and maintain frontend applications.
- Implement a chat application by integrating SendBird's chat API.
- Coordinate with UI/UX to implement designs for our web applications using tools such as Abstract, Zeplin and Invision.
- Collaborated with compliance to make sure our software complies with the laws.
- Use NodeJS, Docker, and PostgreSQL to build server side services for automating payments.
- Participated in typical software development process such as sprint meetings, and code reviews.
- Autonomously outline work and set backlog along with prioritization.
- Help our recruitment team with proctoring new tech candidates in our hackathon.

**Freelance** Malaysia

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

· Use Django, and Django Rest Framework to build a REST API for an over-the-counter payment tracking service.

· Collaborated with project managers, company owners and other engineers over the internet to work on projects requested.

## **Education**

## **University Tunku Abdul Rahman**

Kampar, Perak, Malaysia

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION SYSTEMS (HONOURS) INFORMATION SYSTEMS ENGINEERING

May. 2021 - May. 2024

Jul. 2017 - Jun. 2018

3.0 CGPA

• Obtained an A- in "Data Structure and Algorithmic Problem Solving" which is a course introducing students to data structure and algorithms.